<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Technical Notes for Cloud Services on Cloud 101 Site</title>
    <link>https://sjainout.github.io/cloud/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Technical Notes for Cloud Services on Cloud 101 Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 22:39:34 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sjainout.github.io/cloud/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SRM AVS Install</title>
      <link>https://sjainout.github.io/cloud/srm/srm_avs_install/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 11:41:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sjainout.github.io/cloud/srm/srm_avs_install/</guid>
      <description>Deployment Information AVS DR w/ VMware&amp;rsquo;s SRM Installation Information</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HCX AVS Install</title>
      <link>https://sjainout.github.io/cloud/hcx/hcx_avs_install/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 22:33:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sjainout.github.io/cloud/hcx/hcx_avs_install/</guid>
      <description>Pre-Deployment Information Deployment details On-prem HCX install requirements On-prem HCX ports On-prem HCX IP requirements: 4x IP Addresses for HCX Appliances 3x management IPs 1x will be for the HCX Manager 1x will be for each Interconnect Appliance 1x will be for each Network Extension Appliance 1x vMotion IP for each Interconnect Appliance to participate in vMotion (optional) DNS A record is needeed for on-prem HCX connector to map it’s static IP with it&amp;rsquo;s FQDN name Additional details which will be needed during deployment and configuration: vCenter URL PSC URL vCenter admin credentials DNS Server IP NTP Server IP Proxy Server (optional) Storage for HCX deployment Cluster w/ test workload VMs vDS w/ Port Group for L2 extension AVS HCX Manager Deployment AVS Side HCX Deployment</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Application DR architecture keeping same IP</title>
      <link>https://sjainout.github.io/cloud/srm/srm_hcx_same_ip_architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 13:20:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sjainout.github.io/cloud/srm/srm_hcx_same_ip_architecture/</guid>
      <description>DR steady state Protected site: On-Prem Recovery site: AVS DR Platform: VMware Site Recovery Protected VMs: 3 On-Prem VMs replicated in SRM Port Group (PG) Placeholder VMs: 3 AVS placeholder VMs created on recovery site and kept up to date DR Test DR test platform: Site Recovery Manager (SRM) DR test network: Isolated Segment in AVS DR Migration DR migration platform: Site Recovery Manager (SRM) Protected VMs: 3 On-Prem VMs will be shutdown Recovery VMs: 3 AVS VMs will be powered on Recovery VM network: Layer 2 extended network Network extension platform: HCX DR Event Protected Site: no longer available Recovery Site: AVS Recovery VMs: all VMs come up on AVS Recovery VM network: Layer 3 segment Recovery network platform: NSX-t (part of AVS) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HCX On-Prem Connector OVA Download</title>
      <link>https://sjainout.github.io/cloud/hcx/hcx_on_prem_download/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 08:50:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sjainout.github.io/cloud/hcx/hcx_on_prem_download/</guid>
      <description>Documentation
login to cloud HCX manager get cloud HCX manager URL AVS &amp;gt; Add-ons &amp;gt; Migration using HCX &amp;gt; HCX Cloud Manager IP get cloud HCX manager login credentials AVS &amp;gt; Identity &amp;gt; vCenter &amp;gt; Admin username AVS &amp;gt; Identity &amp;gt; vCenter &amp;gt; Admin password
(do not select &amp;lsquo;Generate a new password&amp;rsquo;)
open browser to cloud HCX manager Use the IP, username and password gathered from earlier steps to go to https:// download on-prem HCX Connector OVA request download link HCX &amp;gt; Administrator &amp;gt; System Updates</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disaster and Backup Recovery Architecture</title>
      <link>https://sjainout.github.io/cloud/srm/srm_dr_backup_architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 09:56:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sjainout.github.io/cloud/srm/srm_dr_backup_architecture/</guid>
      <description>DR and Backup steady state Application Tiers: Essential: consists of shared platform services examples of essential services: Active Directory, Firewall, Loadbalancer, etc these services are setup in active/active or active/standby format Disaster Recovery Backup Recovery </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AVS Internet Access Architecture Options</title>
      <link>https://sjainout.github.io/cloud/avs/avs_internet_access/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 17:06:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sjainout.github.io/cloud/avs/avs_internet_access/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AVS NSXT NVA Architectures</title>
      <link>https://sjainout.github.io/cloud/avs/avs_nsxt_nva_architectures/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 16:13:18 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sjainout.github.io/cloud/avs/avs_nsxt_nva_architectures/</guid>
      <description>Customer can deploy self-managed NVAs like FireWall, Loadbalancer, etc, inside of AVS Private Cloud. From NSX-T&amp;rsquo;s point of view it is just another Virtual Machine (VM).
Here, NVA has to be in routed path, where, it acts as network gateway for the layer 3 segment. From scale point of view, ESXi supports 10 network interfaces per VM. 1 interface can be used for uplink 1 for management 8 segments are then left to create security zones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://sjainout.github.io/cloud/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 08:50:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sjainout.github.io/cloud/about/</guid>
      <description>Sunil Jain
VMware Cloud Solution Architect
(past: Cisco, SAP)
email
linkedin</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AVS Reservation</title>
      <link>https://sjainout.github.io/cloud/avs/avs_reservation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 22:32:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sjainout.github.io/cloud/avs/avs_reservation/</guid>
      <description>Azure VMware Solution (AVS) Host Reservation Introduction AVS host by default are created using on-demand billing rates but if Reserved Instance (RI) for AVS host is purchased then customer can reduce the overall billing commitment.
Azure AVS Reserved Instance Documentation covers 2 routes:
Buy Reserved Instances for an Enterprise Agreement (EA) subscription Buy Reserved Instances for a Cloud Solution Provider (CSP) subscription Requirements AVS Subscription value AVS Region Reservation duration: 1 year or 3 years Payment duration: upfront or monthly Number of hosts to reserve User purchasing the reservation should have at least one of these roles: 1.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
