<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Azure VMware Solution on Cloud 101 Site</title>
    <link>https://sjainout.github.io/cloud/avs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Azure VMware Solution on Cloud 101 Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 23:28:36 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sjainout.github.io/cloud/avs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AVS Internet Access Architecture Options</title>
      <link>https://sjainout.github.io/cloud/avs/avs_internet_access/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 17:06:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sjainout.github.io/cloud/avs/avs_internet_access/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AVS NSXT NVA Architectures</title>
      <link>https://sjainout.github.io/cloud/avs/avs_nsxt_nva_architectures/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 16:13:18 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sjainout.github.io/cloud/avs/avs_nsxt_nva_architectures/</guid>
      <description>Customer can deploy self-managed NVAs like FireWall, Loadbalancer, etc, inside of AVS Private Cloud. From NSX-T&amp;rsquo;s point of view it is just another Virtual Machine (VM).
Here, NVA has to be in routed path, where, it acts as network gateway for the layer 3 segment. From scale point of view, ESXi supports 10 network interfaces per VM. 1 interface can be used for uplink 1 for management 8 segments are then left to create security zones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AVS Reservation</title>
      <link>https://sjainout.github.io/cloud/avs/avs_reservation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 22:32:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sjainout.github.io/cloud/avs/avs_reservation/</guid>
      <description>Azure VMware Solution (AVS) Host Reservation Introduction AVS host by default are created using on-demand billing rates but if Reserved Instance (RI) for AVS host is purchased then customer can reduce the overall billing commitment.
Azure AVS Reserved Instance Documentation covers 2 routes:
Buy Reserved Instances for an Enterprise Agreement (EA) subscription Buy Reserved Instances for a Cloud Solution Provider (CSP) subscription Requirements AVS Subscription value AVS Region Reservation duration: 1 year or 3 years Payment duration: upfront or monthly Number of hosts to reserve User purchasing the reservation should have at least one of these roles: 1.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
